<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Mahalaya App</string>

    <!-- SplashScreenActivity -->
    <string name="app_motive">An innovative and automated way of listening to Mahalaya!</string>
    <string name="developer">Developer: Wrichik Basu @ Basulabs</string>
    <string name="pic_alt_text">Durga picture</string>

    <!-- DateTimeActivity -->
    <string name="date_time_act_label">Date and Time Settings:</string>
    <string name="today_btn_label">Set up program for today at 4am</string>
    <string name="tomorrow_btn_label">Set up program for tomorrow at 4am</string>
    <string name="manual_set_btn_label">Manually set up a date and time</string>
    <string name="proceed_to_media_file">Proceed to Select Media File</string>

    <!-- ManualDateActivity -->
    <string name="date_act_label">Select the date:</string>
    <string name="proceed_time_label">Proceed to set time</string>

    <!-- ManualTimeActivity -->
    <string name="time_act_label">Select the time:</string>

    <!-- ActivityFiles -->
    <string name="choose_file">Choose the media file</string>
    <string name="choose_file_desc">This app does <b>not</b> come with the Mahalaya media
    file. If you haven\'t downloaded it yet, scroll down to find the links for downloading. Once the download is
    over, choose the file by the above button. The file may be placed in SD card or the internal storage.</string>
    <string name="selected_file_label">Selected file:</string>
    <string name="default_file">No file selected!</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start program</string>

    <!-- CountdownActivity -->
    <string name="ctda_date_label">Date set:</string>
    <string name="ctda_time_label">Time set:</string>
    <string name="ctda_time_left_label">Time left:</string>
    <string name="ctda_default_date">01.1.1970</string>
    <string name="ctda_default_time">00:00</string>
    <string name="default_time_left">Calculating…</string>
    <string name="ctda_abort_button">Abort program</string>
    <string name="vol_ctrl_label">Volume controls:</string>
    <string name="set_volume_label">Set playback volume:</string>
    <string name="marquee_volume_reminder">Remember to set a decent media volume!</string>

    <!-- MahalayaService -->
    <string name="default_time_left_notif">Calculating time left…</string>
    <string name="request_focus_notif">Requesting Audio Focus from the system…</string>

    <!-- MediaPlayerActivity -->
    <string name="mpa_default_media_state">Determining media state…</string>
    <string name="mpa_abort_button">Abort playing media</string>

    <!-- ThankYouActivity -->
    <string name="morning">Good Morning!</string>
    <string name="what_the_app_has_done">This app has played Mahalaya at the time set by you.</string>
    <string name="thanks">Thank you for using this app.</string>
    <string name="wish">Have a great time during the Puja!</string>

    <!-- Miscellaneous -->
    <plurals name="day">
        <item quantity="one">day</item>
        <item quantity="other">days</item>
    </plurals>
    <plurals name="hour">
        <item quantity="one">hour</item>
        <item quantity="other">hours</item>
    </plurals>
    <plurals name="mins">
        <item quantity="one">minute</item>
        <item quantity="other">minutes</item>
    </plurals>
    <plurals name="secs">
        <item quantity="one">second.</item>
        <item quantity="other">seconds.</item>
    </plurals>
    <string name="day_short">d</string>
    <string name="hour_short">h</string>
    <string name="minute_short">m</string>
    <string name="second_short">s.</string>
    <string name="time_up">Time UP!</string>
    <string name="and"> and </string>
    <string name="media_playing">Media is playing.</string>
    <string name="media_paused">Playback is paused.</string>
    <string name="time_left_notif">Time left: </string>
    <string name="playback_complete">Playback complete. Tap to know more.</string>

    <!-- Theme -->
    <string name="choose_theme">Choose theme:</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="time">Set by time</string>
    <string name="system">Set by system</string>
    <string name="set_theme">Apply</string>

    <!-- AlertBox -->
    <string name="message_alert">Once the program is started, date and time cannot be changed.</string>
    <string name="alert_cont">Continue</string>
    <string name="alert_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Toolbar -->
    <string name="theme">Enable/Disable dark theme</string>
    <string name="help">How to use this app?</string>

    <!-- Toast -->
    <string name="date_success">Date picked successfully</string>
    <string name="time_success">Time picked successfully.</string>
    <string name="toast_today">Program set for today at 4 am</string>
    <string name="toast_tomorrow">Program set for tomorrow at 4 am</string>
    <string name="past_time">Time chosen is in the past!</string>
    <string name="execution_cancel">Execution cancelled</string>

    <!-- HowToActivity -->
    <string name="how_to_label">How to use this app</string>
    <string name="how_to_text_content">

        Welcome to the Mahalaya app!\n\n

        In this app, you can set the date and time when you want Mahalaya to be played. When the time comes,
        the app will automatically play Mahalaya using its inbuilt media player. This means that you do not
        need to download any third-party media player.\n\n

        After the splash screen, you will have a screen showing you four options:\n
            1. Set program for today at 4 am,\n
            2. Set program for tomorrow at 4 am,\n
            3. Manually set a date and time, and\n
            4. Proceed to chose the files.\n\n

        The first two will automatically set the date and time as they state. The first option may not be available
        depending on when you are starting the program. The third option will allow you to set a date
        and time according to your wish. You will be directed to a screen where you will can choose a date. After clicking
        <code>Proceed to set time</code>, you will go to another screen where you will be able to set the time.
        After this, you are required to select the media file.\n\n

        If you choose any of the first two options, then you can directly go to media file selection screen by clicking on option 4.\n\n

        Unfortunately this app does <b>not</b> contain the media file for Mahalaya. The size of the file is about 150 MB
        in mp4 format, and hence I decided not to pack that file with the app so that while downloading, your internal
        storage doesn\'t get full all of a sudden and your phone crashes. You can download the media file in mp4 or mp3
        format from Google Drive through the links at the end.\n\n

        Either after choosing options 1 or 2 from above, or after setting the time (i.e. if you chose option 3),
        you have to select the media file. This file can be placed anywhere - the internal storage or the
        microSD card, whichever is suitable for you. In the media selection screen, when you click on "Choose a media file",
        the file browser opens where you can select the file. Currently supported formats are mp4 and mp3 only. When you select
        the file, its path will be visible in the media selection screen.\n\n

        Now you can start the program. Remember, once you do that, you cannot change the date and time
        without aborting the current instance of the program.\n\n

        Once the countdown starts, you will be taken to a screen where you will be able to see the time left for Mahalaya
        to start. There will be an ongoing notification that will also show you the time left. You can safely
        exit the countdown screen; that will not hamper the program. If you click on the notification, you can come back to the
        this screen again.\n\n

        The countdown screen also has an abort button. In case you want to stop the program, click this button.\n\n

        Please remember to set a decent volume for the media player. If the media stream is muted, you
        will not be able to hear anything when Mahalaya starts.\n\n

        Once the time arrives, the playback will start automatically. There will be a notification that will allow you to
        pause or re-start the media player. Clicking on this notification will take you to a screen that will show the time
        left for the media to end. There will be an abort button here as well, which will completely stop the playback and kill the app.\n\n

        You can change the theme of the app by clicking the bulb icon in the toolbar.\n\n

        If you have any question or suggestion, feel free to drop me an email at <a href="mailto:basulabs.developer@gmail.com">basulabs.developer@gmail.com</a>
        and I shall be happy to help. If you have found a bug, please mention the exact steps so that I can reproduce it.
        A screen video will also be very helpful.\n\n

        Thank you for trying this app.\n\n

        The media download links are available below.
    </string>
    <string name="mp4_download">Download media file in mp4 format</string>
    <string name="mp3_download">Download media file in mp3 format</string>

    <string name="dont_have_file">Links to download the media file:</string>
    <string name="vol_ctrl_check_box">Allow this app to change media stream volume</string>


</resources>
